(
"ai_sub_version": "3.6.0",
"generated_at": "2026-10-10T13:07:06.745818",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"service_tier": null,
"service_tier_subtitles": null,
"service_tier_lyrics": null,
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
あの、Count Night TVが2年ぶりに大復活！？
That Count Night TV is making a grand return after two years?!
さらにパワーアップして帰ってきました！
And it's back, powered up even more!
今年の生誕は、懐かしのアニソンロックを
For this year's birthday, nostalgic anime song rock
姫森ルーナがランキング形式で歌います！
Himemori Luna will sing in a ranking format!
懐かしのあの曲や…えっ、あの曲まで！？
From those nostalgic songs... wait, even that song?!
ド派手な野外ステージ！
On an extravagant outdoor stage!
Count Night TV Evolution、開幕です！
Count Night TV Evolution, now opening!
このあとすぐ！みんな、絶対絶対見てなのらねー！
Coming up right after! Everyone, you absolutely must watch!
こんばんは！Count Night TVです！
Good evening! This is Count Night TV!
この番組は名誉ルーナイトであるポルナイトと、フブルーナイトが司会でお送りする音楽ランキング番組です！
This music ranking show is hosted by Polunight, an honorary Roonight, and Fubulunight!
前回のCount Night TVがさらにパワーアップ！副題の通りエボリューションしております！
The previous Count Night TV is powered up even more! As the subtitle says, it's evolving!
今回は特設野外フェスステージからお送りさせていただきます！
This time, we're bringing it to you from a special outdoor festival stage!
パワーアップの名にふさわしい仕掛けがあるとかないとか…楽しみにしていてくださいね！そうして！
There may or may not be tricks worthy of the power-up name... Please look forward to it! And so!
今日のハッシュタグはこちら！#姫森ルーナ生誕ロックLIVEで拡散してね！
Today's hashtag is right here! Spread it with #HimemoriLunaBirthdayRockLIVE!
ということで、本日のランキングテーマは、姫森ルーナ厳選！ロックなアニソン特集TOP10！とのことですが、
With that said, today's ranking theme is Himemori Luna's carefully selected Rock Anime Song Special TOP 10!
どんな曲がランクインしているのでしょうか？
What kind of songs have made the ranking?
それではまず、10位から8位まで見ていきましょう！
Well then, let's first take a look from 10th to 8th place!
Count Night！
Count Night!
大キライだったそばかすをちょっと
Those freckles I used to hate so much...
ひととなしてため息をひとつ
I let out a single sigh.
ヘヴィー級の恋はみごとに角砂糖と一緒に溶けた
My heavyweight love melted away completely right along with a sugar cube.
前よりももっとやせた胸にちょっと
On my chest, even thinner than before,
チクッとささるトゲがイタイ
a prickly thorn stings and hurts.
星占いもあてにならないわ
Even horoscope readings aren't reliable.
もっと遠くまで 一緒にゆけたら ねえ
If we could go even further together, hey,
うれしくて それだけで
I'd be so happy, just with that.
想い出は いつも キレイだけど
Memories are always beautiful, but
それだけじゃ おなかがすくわ
that alone leaves me hungry.
本当は せつない夜なのに
Even though it's truly a heartbreaking night...
Even though it's actually a painful night,
どうしてかしら？
Why is it?
あの人の笑顔も
I can't even remember
思い出せないの
that person's smile.
こわして なおして わかってるのに
Breaking it, fixing it, even though I know...
それが あたしの 性格だから
That's just my personality,
もどかしい気持ちで あやふやなままで
with this frustrating feeling, remaining vague,
それでも イイ 恋をしてきた
even so, I've had good love affairs.
おもいきりあげた
Opening it wide open,
左耳のピアスには ねえ
the earring in my left ear, hey...
笑えない エピソード
an episode I can't laugh about.
Wow Wow
そばかすの数を かぞえてみる
I try counting the number of freckles.
汚れたぬいぐるみ抱いて
Hugging a dirty stuffed animal,
胸をさす トゲは 消えないけど
the thorn piercing my chest won't go away, but
カエルちゃんも ウサギちゃんも
both the frog and the rabbit
笑ってくれるの
will smile for me.
想い出は いつも キレイだけど
Memories are always beautiful, but
それだけじゃ おなかが すくの
just that isn't enough to fill my stomach.
本当は せつない夜なのに
Even though it's actually a painful night,
どうしてかしら？
Why is it?
あの人の涙も
I can't even remember
思い出せないの
that person's tears either.
I can't remember them.
Wow wow La la...
どうしてなの？
Why is it?
Please don't say "You are lazy" だって本当は crazy
Please don't say "You are lazy," because actually I'm crazy.
白鳥たちはそう 見えないとこでバタ足するんです
Swans, you see, are paddling furiously where you can't see.
本能に従順忠実 翻弄も重々承知
Obedient and faithful to instinct, fully aware of being toyed with,
前途洋々だし…だからたまに休憩しちゃうんです
the future is bright... that's why I take a break sometimes.
この目でしっかり見定めて 行き先図上マークして
Looking closely with these eyes, marking the destination on the map,
近道あればそれが王道 はしゃめる翼があれば上等
if there's a shortcut that's the royal road, if there are wings to frolic with, even better,
ヤバ 爪割れた グルーで補修した
Yikes, a broken nail, repaired it with glue,
それだけでなんか達成感
just that gives me a sense of accomplishment.
大事なのは自分 かワイがること
The important thing is to cherish yourself.
自分を愛さなきゃ 他人も愛せない
If you don't love yourself, you can't love others either.
Please don't say "You are lazy" だって本当は crazy
Please don't say "You are lazy," because actually I'm crazy.
能ある鷹はそう 見えないとこにピック隠すんです
A skilled hawk, you see, hides its pick where you can't see.
想像に一生懸命 現実は絶体絶命
Working so hard in imagination, reality is desperate,
発展途中だし…だから不意にピッチ外れるんです
still a work in progress... that's why my pitch suddenly goes off.
その目に映らないだけだって やる気はメーター振り切って
It's just not visible to those eyes, my motivation is maxed out on the meter.
いつでも全力で夢見て
Always dreaming with all my might,
その分全力で眠って
Sleeping just as hard to balance it out.
ヤリちょい痩せた 調子づいて喰った
I lost a little weight and got cocky, overeating—
それだけでなんで？ 敗北感
why does just that give me a sense of defeat?
すかさずに目標 下方修正して
Quickly revising my goals downward,
柔軟に臨機応変 七変化が勝ち
being flexible and adaptable, versatility wins!
Please don't say "You are lazy"
だって本当はcrazy
'cause I'm actually crazy.
孔雀たちはそう ここぞというとき美を魅せるんです
Peacocks, you see, show their beauty when it counts the most.
五臓六腑 満身 邁進 願望は身心 満人
Body and soul, charging ahead, my desire is total fulfillment—
誘惑多発だし… 脳内年中常時
temptations are frequent... constantly active in my mind,
だからやけに息切れしちゃうんです
so I end up getting out of breath for no reason.
ヤバ まさか赤点！？ いや ギリクリア！
Oh no, could it be a failing grade?! No, barely passing!
それだけでなんて 全能感
Just from that, such a sense of omnipotence—
大事なのは自分 認めてくこと
the important thing is acknowledging yourself.
自分を許さなきゃ 他人も許せない
If you can't forgive yourself, you can't forgive others either.
Please don't say "You are lazy"
だって本当はcrazy
'cause I'm actually crazy.
白鳥たちはそう 見えないとこでバタ足するんです
Swans, you see, are paddling frantically where you can't see.
本能に従順 忠実 翻弄も直々承知 前途洋々だし…
Subservient to instinct, fully aware of being tossed about, the future is bright—
だからたまに休憩しちゃうんです
so I take a little break every now and then.
目まぐるしい 時間の群れが
A dizzying swarm of time
走り抜ける 都市はサバンナ
running through the city, a savanna.
かわるがわる シュールなニュース
Alternating surreal news—
明日になれば 誰も忘れてる
by tomorrow, everyone will have forgotten.
生きている 今 生きている
I'm alive, right now I'm alive,
そんな中で 何かを求め もがくように 抜け出すように
in the midst of it all, seeking something, struggling to break free,
この力を 試してみたいくて
wanting to test this power of mine.
きっとどこかに「答」ある
Surely, somewhere there is an "answer"—
生まれてきた答えが 人は皆 それを求め
the answer to why we were born, which everyone seeks.
やるせない のがせない 夢に向かうの
Heartbreaking, unmissable, heading toward my dream—
傷つく事は 恐くない だけど決して強くない
being hurt isn't scary, but I'm certainly not strong.
ただ 何もしないままで 悔やんだりはしたくない
Yet I don't want to regret just doing nothing.
Here we go! go! 走り続ける 誰にも止められはしない
Here we go! go! Keep running, no one can stop me!
未来の自分へと Give a reason for life 届けたい
Toward my future self, Give a reason for life, I want to deliver it!
計り知れない 大きな闇が 音を立てて 向かって来ても
Even if an unfathomable, massive darkness approaches making a sound,
朝が来れば 誰かがいれば 心にある 絶望は消せる
if morning comes, if someone is there, the despair in your heart can be erased.
もっと強くイメージして 微笑んでる自分を…
Imagine yourself even stronger, smiling...
信じてる想い それが 何よりも 誰よりも 夢に近づく
The feeling of belief brings you closer to your dreams than anything or anyone else.
ゴールにもたれたりしない たとえ 辿り着いたって
I won't lean on the goal, even if I finally reach it.
たとい 辿り着いたって
Even if I reach it,
新しい夢がきっと 私の背中押すから
a new dream will surely push my back.
Here we go! go! 走り続ける
Here we go! go! I'll keep running
誰にも止められはしない
No one can stop me.
未来の自分へと Give a reason for life
Toward my future self, Give a reason for life,
光り輝きと 届けたい
I want to deliver the shining brilliance.
きっとどこかに「答え」ある
Surely, there's an answer somewhere,
生まれたきた答えが
the answer to why I was born.
人は皆それを求め
Everyone seeks it,
やるせない のがせない 夢に向かうの
heading toward dreams that can't be helped or missed.
傷つくことは怖くない
Being hurt is not scary,
だけどけして強くない
yet I'm not that strong.
ただ 何もしないままで
I don't want to regret
悔やんだりしたくない
just doing nothing.
Here we go! go! 走り続ける
Here we go! go! I'll keep running,
誰にも止められはしない
no one can stop me.
未来の自分へと Give a reason for life
Toward my future self, Give a reason for life,
光り輝きと 届けたい
I want to deliver the shining brilliance.
ということで、3曲連続で歌っていただきました！
And with that, she sang three songs in a row!
モニターがぽこんって開いたよ！
The monitor just popped right open!
今回も姫のために番組粘土予算をすべて使って、素晴らしいステージを用意させていただきました！
This time too, we used the entire show budget for the Princess to prepare a wonderful stage!
お次は7位から5位までの発表です。
Next up is the announcement from 7th to 5th place.
このあとは私たちも踊っちゃうかも？
After this, maybe we'll dance too?
せーの、カウントナイト！
Ready, set, Count Night!
Over The Future
[7: Over The Future]
only my railgun
[6: only my railgun]
God knows...
[5: God knows...]
かなりきてる 無敵のパワー！
It's coming on strong, invincible power!
マジでいいカンジ
It feels seriously great!
絶対可憐！だから負けない！
Absolutely lovely! That's why I won't lose!
明日へ さあ行こう！
Let's go now, toward tomorrow!
絶対！
Yeah! Absolutely!
大胆！
Bold!
最大！
Maximum!
Yeah! Maximum!
大胆！ 最大！ 大胆！
Bold! Maximum! Bold!
ただ待っているだけの 今日を脱ぎ捨てて
Cast off today, where I was just waiting around,
WAKU WAKU できる今日を手にしたい
and get a thrilling day I can look forward to!
触れ合うだけでわかる 心のリミッター
The limiter of the heart, understood just by touching,
解き放たれたら ホラ Yes! Change the world!
once unleashed, look! Yes! Change the world!
熱いバトル 何度もトライ！
A fierce battle, try it again and again!
リアルをつらぬいて
Push through reality!
絶対可憐！だから負けない！
Absolutely lovely! That's why I won't lose!
スリルがサイコー！
The thrill is the best!
勇気が世界の闇を 照らし始める
Courage begins to shed light on the darkness of the world.
あなたがくれた奇跡あふれる
Overflowing with the miracles you gave me,
誰にも似てない笑顔 誇りにしたら
If I take pride in a smile like no one else's,
未来を今超えよう
let's surpass the future right now!
Yeah!
絶対！ 大胆！
Absolutely! Bold!
最大！ 大胆！
Yeah! Maximum! Bold!
こんな困難だって 案外平気だし
Even difficulties like this are surprisingly fine,
DOKI DOKI しながらまたハマってく
heart pounding, I'll fall into it all over again.
てゆーか「待ってるのはラクだけじゃない」こと
I'm starting to realize that "waiting around isn't the only easy thing,"
わかり始めてるから Don't lose my way!
so Don't lose my way!
傷つくのも恐れないで どこにでも行ける
Without fear of getting hurt, I can go anywhere.
絶対可憐！それがポリシー！ 痛みも楽しめる
Absolutely lovely! That's my policy! I can even enjoy the pain.
涙は夢のありかを 探す輝き
Tears are the brilliance searching for where dreams lie.
Tears are the radiance searching for where dreams reside,
それぞれ違う光を放つ
each emitting a different light.
悲しみ抱え込むなら 私も泣こう
If you're harboring sorrow, I'll cry too,
未来はこの手にある
the future is in these hands.
勇気が世界の闇を 照らし始める
Courage begins to illuminate the world's darkness,
あなたがくれた奇跡あふれる
overflowing with the miracles you gave me.
誰にも似てない笑顔 誇りにしたら
If I make this unique smile my pride,
未来を今超えよう
let's surpass the future right now!
We can try over the future world!!
放て！心に刻んだ夢を 未来さえ置き去りにして
Unleash the dream carved in your heart, leaving even the future behind!
限界など知らない 意味無い！
Knowing no limits, it's meaningless!
この能力が光放らす その先に遥かな想いを
Beyond where this power radiates lies a distant desire.
歩いてきた この道を 振り返ることしか
Can I only look back at the path I've walked down
出来ないなら…今ここで全てを壊せる
if I can't... then I'll destroy everything right here.
暗闇に堕ちる街並み 人はどこまで立ち向かえるの？
How far can humanity stand against the cityscape falling into darkness?
加速するその痛みから 誰かをきっと守れるよ
Surely I can protect someone from that accelerating pain.
Looking! The blitz loop this planet to search way.
Only my RAILGUN can shoot it. 今すぐ
Only my RAILGUN can shoot it right now.
身体中を 光の速さで 駆け巡った 確かな予感
A certain premonition raced through my body at the speed of light.
掴め！望むものなら残さず 輝ける自分らしさで
Seize it! Whatever you desire, leave nothing behind, with your radiant self.
信じるよ あの日の誓いを この瞳に光る涙 それさえも強さに なるから
I believe in that day's vow—even the tears shining in these eyes will become strength.
立ち止まると 少しだけ 感じる切なさに
When I stop, I feel a slight sorrow,
戸惑う事 無いなんて 嘘はつかないよ
I won't lie and say I have no hesitations.
宙に舞うコインが描く 放物線が定める運命
The parabola drawn by the coin dancing in the air determines fate.
打ち出した答えが今日も 私の胸を駆け巡る
The answer I struck out races through my heart today as well.
Sparkling! The shiny lights awake true desire.
Only my RAILGUN can shoot it. 必ず
Only my RAILGUN can shoot it for sure.
貫いてく 迷うことなく 傷ついても 走り続ける
Piercing through without hesitation, continuing to run even when hurt.
狙え！凛と煌く視線は 狂い無く闇を切り裂く
Aim! A dignified and sparkling gaze tears through the darkness without fail.
迷いなんて 吹き飛ばせばいい この心が叫ぶ限り 誰ひとり邪魔などさせない
Just blow away any hesitation; as long as this heart screams, I won't let anyone get in my way.
儚く舞う 無数の願いは この両手に積もってゆく
Countless transient wishes pile up in these hands.
切り裂く闇に見えてくるのは 重く深く 切ない記憶
What comes into view in the torn-down darkness is heavy, deep, and painful memories.
色褪せてく 現実に揺れる 絶望には 負けたくない
Fading, swaying in reality, I don't want to lose to despair.
私が今 私であること 胸を張って 全て誇れる！
Holding my head high, I can be proud of everything that I am right now!
Looking! The blitz loop this planet to search way.
Only my RAILGUN can shoot it. 今すぐ
Only my RAILGUN can shoot it right now.
身体中を 光の速さで 駆け巡った 確かな予感
A certain premonition rushed through my body at the speed of light.
放て！心に刻んだ夢を 未来さえ置き去りにして
Release the dream carved in your heart, leaving even the future behind!
限界など知らない 意味無い！この能力が光放つ その先に遥かな想いを
Knowing no limits, it's meaningless! Far beyond where this power radiates its light...
渇いた心で駆け抜ける
Running through with a parched heart.
ごめんね何もできなくて
I'm sorry I couldn't do anything for you.
痛みを分かち合うことさえ
Even sharing our pain...
あなたは許してくれない
You won't forgive me for it.
無垢に生きるため振り向かず
Without looking back, to live innocently,
背中向けて 去ってしまう on the lonely rail
I turn my back and walk away on the lonely rail.
私ついていくよ どんな辛い世界の闇の中でさえ
I will follow you, even in the darkness of any painful world,
きっとあなたは輝いて 超える未来の果て
I'm sure you will shine, beyond the horizon of the future.
弱さ故に魂こわされないように my way 重なるよ
So that my soul isn't destroyed by weakness, my way overlaps with yours.
いまふたりに God bless...
God bless the two of us right now...
届けて熱くなる想いは
Conveying these burning feelings,
現実溶かしてさまよう
I wander, melting reality.
会いたい気持ちに理由はない
There's no reason for wanting to see you.
あなたへあふだす Lovin' you
Overflowing toward you, Lovin' you.
せめて美しい夢だけを
At least, drawing only a beautiful dream,
描きながら 追いかけよう for your lonely heart
I'll chase it for your lonely heart.
やめて嘘はあなたらしくないよ
Stop lying, it's not like you.
目を見てこれからのことを話そう
Look me in the eyes and let's talk about the future.
私覚悟してる
I am prepared.
暗い未来だって強くなって運命変えられるかもね
Even a dark future—if I become strong, maybe I can change fate.
my wish 叶えたいのに すべては God knows...
Even though I want my wish to come true, everything is... God knows...
あなたがいて 私がいて
With you here, with me here,
ほかの人は消えてしまった
everyone else has disappeared.
淡い夢の美しさを描きながら
While portraying the beauty of a fleeting dream,
傷跡なぞる
I trace the scars.
だから
That's why...
私ついていくよ どんな辛い世界の闇の中でさえ きっとあなたは輝いて
I will follow you, even in the darkness of any painful world, I'm sure you will shine...
超える未来の果て 弱さ故に魂こわされないように my way 重なるよ
Beyond the horizon of the future, so that my soul isn't destroyed by weakness, my way overlaps with yours.
いまふたりに God bless...
God bless the two of us right now...
平成の記憶が蘇るセトリですねー！
Heisei memories are coming back with this setlist!
「OVER THE FUTURE」では姫と一緒に踊れてポルナイト感激です！
Dancing with Hime to "OVER THE FUTURE"—Porunaito is thrilled!
おっと、ポルナイトの号泣に合わせてお空も雨模様に？
Oh, and with Porunaito's wailing, the skies turned rainy too?
まあ、野外ならではの醍醐味ですねー！
Well, that's the real charm of an outdoor venue!
さてさて、ランキングは残すところ上位から1位までとなりました！
Now then, the ranking is down to the top songs, 1st place!
何の曲が1位になるんでしょうか！？
Which song will claim the number one spot!?
それでは雨にも負けず皆さんご一緒に！
Now, rain or shine, everyone together!
カウントナイト！
Count Night!
少女S
[Title: Shoujo S]
さっきまでと言ってること違うじゃない
It's different from what you were saying just a moment ago.
ちょっとだけ素顔見せたけれど
Though you showed your true face just a little,
ずっとイライライライライラしては
Constantly irritated and edgy,
あたしをモノみたいに扱って
treating me like an object.
さっきまでと言ってること違うじゃない
It's different from what you were saying just a moment ago.
誰かのせいにしては 逃げ隠れしてる日々
Days of hiding and running away, blaming someone else.
アテにならないわ
You're unreliable.
I'm sorry とりあえずサヨナラ
I'm sorry, goodbye for now.
あなたがいないとイヤイヤって言えるわがまま
The selfishness of saying "I hate it if you're not here."
(ずっと消えないように 消さないように)
(So it never fades, so it never gets erased)
愛情? 友情? 知りたいことは何でも
Affection? Friendship? Whatever I want to know,
(曖昧すぎてわからないよ)
(It's too vague, I don't understand)
いつか心の奥のドアを叩く あなたを待っている
Waiting for you to someday knock on the door deep in my heart.
さっきから自分のことばっかりじゃない
It's been all about yourself from a moment ago.
ちょっとぐらい気付いてみたら？
Why don't you notice just a little?
そうやって優しい言葉で誤魔化しないで
Don't brush it off with gentle words like that.
信じられないわ かっこつけないでよ
I can't believe it, don't try to look cool.
何年たってもいつになっても
No matter how many years pass, no matter when,
あたしがいないとダメダメって言って素直に
honestly say "You're no good without me."
(もっと欲しがってよ 強がらないで)
(Want me more, don't act tough)
愛の残像 夢見る少女エスケープ
Afterimage of love, dreaming girl's escape.
(捕まったり 逃げ切ったり)
(Getting caught or managing to escape)
いつか心のカギを壊すような…
Someday, like breaking the key of the heart...
あなたがいないとイヤイヤって言えるわがまま
The selfishness of saying "I hate it if you're not here."
(ずっと消えないように 消さないように)
(So it never fades, so it never gets erased)
愛情? 友情? 知りたいことは何でも
Affection? Friendship? Whatever I want to know,
(曖昧すぎてわからないよ)
(It's too vague, I don't understand)
いつか心の奥を抱いてくれる あなたを待っている
Waiting for you to someday hold the depth of my heart.
他には何もいらないイヤイヤイヤ
I don't need anything else, no, no, no.
明日も信じていたいイヤイヤイヤイヤ…
I want to believe in tomorrow too, no, no, no...
衝動
[Title: Shoudou]
長い夜に目覚めて 青白い部屋の中
Waking up in a long night, inside a pale blue room,
不意に大事な何かを 傷つけたくなる
suddenly wanting to hurt something precious.
(暗闇のfreedom)
(Freedom of darkness)
扉の前で 立ちつくす
Standing still in front of the door.
ちっぽけな 背中に気づいてほしい
I want you to notice my tiny back,
僕にも 誰かを 愛せると
and let me know that I, too, can love someone
その手を 重ねて 知らせて
by overlapping our hands.
あなたのぬくもりがくれる 衝動
The impulse that your warmth gives me...
真実ばかり追いかけて 揺れ動く everyday
Chasing only the truth, my everyday life sways and wavers.
強がる自分の中も まるっきり謎だらけ
Even the inside of my acting-tough self is full of mysteries.
はがねのような 絆だけが
Only a steel-like bond
凹んでく心を 踏ん張らせる
makes my depressed heart hold its ground.
僕にも 何かを変えられる
I, too, can change something.
さりげない 言葉で ささやいて
Whisper to me with casual words;
あなたの声が 明日への 衝動
your voice is the impulse toward tomorrow.
誰もが 無限の可能性を
Everyone embraces infinite possibilities
抱きしめて 生まれてきたんでしょう? ねえ。
since the day they were born, right? Hey.
僕にも 誰かを 愛せると
And let me know that I, too, can love someone
その手を 重ねて 知らせて
by overlapping our hands.
希望とは 目の前にある道
Hope is the path right before our eyes;
どこかに行けると 信じよう
let's believe we can go somewhere.
あなたのすべてが 僕の衝動
Everything about you is my impulse.
go for it go for it
愛情こそが衝動
Affection is truly the impulse!
go for it go for it
愛情こそが衝動
Affection is truly the impulse!
愛に気づいて下さい 僕が抱きしめてあげる
Please realize my love; I will hold you tight.
夢も涙も忘れて 君を求めていた
Forgetting dreams and tears alike, I was searching for you.
誰も知らない世界で 僕がささやいてあげる
In a world where no one knows, I will whisper to you.
窓に映る切なさは 生まれ変わるメロディー
The sorrow reflected in the window is a melody reborn.
壊れてしまった バランスが崩れた
Everything broke down; the balance collapsed.
手探り探す指先が震えて
My groping fingertips are trembling,
戸惑うくせに絡みつく花びらは
and the petals entwine despite my hesitation.
溜め息重ねて 浮かぶイメージ
Piling up sighs, an image floats to the surface.
目を閉じてごらん どこまでも行こう
Close your eyes and let's go anywhere.
鮮やかに奪われた君が離れない
You, vividly swept away, never leave my mind.
愛に気づいて下さい 僕が抱きしめてあげる
Please realize my love; I will hold you tight.
夢も涙も忘れて 君を求めていた
Forgetting dreams and tears alike, I was searching for you.
誰も知らない世界で 僕がささやいてあげる
In a world where no one knows, I will whisper to you.
恋に落ちる切なさは 生まれ変わるメロディー
The sorrow of falling in love is a melody reborn.
夏の雪のように優しい微笑みは
Your gentle smile, like summer snow...
美しい君に遊ぶイメージ
An image of playing with you, so beautiful...
泣かないで僕が側にいるから
Don't cry, because I am right by your side.
完全に奪われた愛が止まらない
My completely stolen love cannot be stopped.
冷めた悲劇のヒロイン 僕があたためてあげる
I'll warm up your cold, tragic heroine heart.
君の眩しい笑顔に 早く会いたいから
Because I want to see your dazzling smile so soon.
声にならないトキメキ うまく歌えない I LOVE YOU
An unspoken excitement, I can't sing it right—I LOVE YOU.
僕の君に届けたい 生まれ変わるメロディー
I want to reach you with a reborn melody.
愛に気づいて下さい 僕が抱きしめてあげる
Please realize my love, I will hold you tight.
夢も涙も忘れて 君を求めていた
Forgetting dreams and tears, I was longing for you.
誰も知らない世界で 僕が囁いてあげる
In a world nobody knows, I will whisper to you.
全て君だけの為に 生まれ変わるメロディー
A reborn melody, all for your sake alone.
愛は幻の中へ
Love drifts into an illusion...
僕は君を見失う
I lose sight of you.
愛に気づいて下さい
Please realize my love.
強く強く抱きしめたい 生まれ変わる天使
I want to hold you tighter and tighter, my reborn angel.
ゴキゲンな蝶になって きらめく風に乗って
Becoming a cheerful butterfly, riding the shimmering wind,
今すぐ キミに会いに行こう
I'm going to see you right now!
余計なことなんて 忘れた方がマシさ
It's better to forget all unnecessary things.
これ以上 シャレてる時間はない
There's no time to be playing around anymore.
何が WOW WOW~ この空に届くだろう
What will reach this sky, WOW WOW~?
だけど WOW WOW~ 明日の予定もわからない
But WOW WOW~ I don't even know tomorrow's plans.
無限大な夢のあとの 何もない世の中じゃ
In a world with nothing left after infinite dreams,
そうさ愛しい 想いも負けそうになるけど
Yes, even such lovely feelings start to feel defeated, but...
Stayしがちなイメージだらけの 頼ない翼でも
Even with untrustworthy wings full of stagnant images,
きっと飛べるさ On My Love
I'm sure we can fly, On My Love!
ウカレタ蝶になって 一途な風に乗って
Becoming a fluttering butterfly, riding the single-minded wind,
どこまでも キミに会いに行こう
I'm going to see you no matter where!
曖昧な言葉って 意外に便利だって
That ambiguous words are surprisingly convenient,
叫んでる ヒットソング聴きながら
While listening to a shouting hit song.
何が WOW WOW~ この街に響くだろう
What will echo through this town, WOW WOW~?
だけど WOW WOW~ 期待してても仕方ない
But WOW WOW~ it's no use expecting anything.
無限大な夢のあとの やるせない世の中じゃ
In a frustrating world after infinite dreams,
そうさ常識 はずれも悪くはないかな
Yes, maybe being a bit unconventional isn't so bad either.
Stayそうなイメージを染めた きこえない翼でも
Even with untrustworthy wings dyed with stray images...
きっと飛べるさ On My Love
I'm sure I can fly, On My Love
無限大な夢のあとの 何もない世の中じゃ
In this empty world after an infinite dream,
何もないような部屋じゃ そうさ愛しい 想いも負けそうになるけど
In a room like nothingness, yes, even my dear feelings feel like they're going to lose, but
Stayしがちなイメージだけの 頼りない翼でも
Even with unreliable wings of mere lingering images,
きっと飛べるさ Oh Yeah~
I'm sure I can fly, Oh Yeah~
無限大な夢のあとの やるせない世の中じゃ
In this frustrating world after an infinite dream,
そうさ常識 はずされも悪くはないかな
That's right, breaking away from common sense isn't so bad either.
Stayそうなイメージを染めた きごこない翼でも
Even with clumsy wings dyed with lingering images,
きっと飛べるさ On My Love
I'm sure I can fly, On My Love
はーい、みんな！
Hi everyone!
ここまで見てくれてありがとー！
Thank you so much for watching this far!
姫森ルーナ生誕ロックLIVEどうだったー？楽しんでくれたなら！
How was Himemori Luna's Birthday Rock LIVE? I hope you enjoyed it!
こちらのね、シャープ姫森ルーナ生誕ロックLIVEで写真いっぱいに投稿してくれたのなら！
If you posted lots of photos with the hashtag #姫森ルーナ生誕ロックLIVE!
まだこの後もね、歌うんだけどもち、ここからは大事なご・こ・ち・た・い・む！
I'll be singing more after this, but now is the important G-O-O-D-S T-I-M-E!
最後までこのまま見てるんならね！
Make sure you stay and watch until the very end!
まずは、1つめー！
First up, item number one!
姫森ルーナ誕生日記念2026のグッズが出てるのなら！
The Himemori Luna Birthday Commemoration 2026 goods are out!
では、詳細を見ていきましょう！
Now, let's take a closer look at the details!
まずは、こちら！ルーナ姫の回転アクリルスタンド！イラストはカッコ可愛いルーナをテーマに、かんざきひろパパに描いてもらったのなら！
First, this! Princess Luna's Rotating Acrylic Stand! The illustration features a cool yet cute Luna, drawn by Kanzaki Hiro-papa!
パパが描いてくれた2種類のイラストが、表と裏の両面で楽しめる1つで2度美味しい回転アクリルスタンドなのだ！
It's a delicious two-in-one rotating acrylic stand where you can enjoy two different illustrations by Papa on both the front and back!
その日の気分に合わせて、クルクルするのなら！
Spin it around to match your mood for the day!
次は、こちら！カッコ可愛いお揃いスタジャン♡ 今回のキービジュアルにも使用している、大人カッコいい衣装のスタジャンを再現したのなら！
Next is this! Cool & Cute Matching Stadium Jacket♡ Recreating the mature and cool stadium jacket used in the key visual!
胸元には衣装とお揃いでルーナへとのししゅうが入ってます！ルーナっ子たち着用必須なのだ！
The chest features embroidery matching Luna's outfit! A must-wear item for all Luna-kko!
次は、こちら！プニプニお揃い缶バッジ♡ 同じくキービジュアルの大人カッコいい衣装に付いてるルーナイトとたこパパの缶バッジをプニプニ素材で作ってみたのだ！スタジャンにつけて衣装を再現してもよし！リュックとかにつけて密かにルーナイトアピールするのもよしなのだ！
Next is this! Squishy Matching Can Badge♡ Made with squishy material featuring the Lunight and Tako-papa can badges from the mature, cool key visual! Put it on your jacket to complete the look, or attach it to your backpack to secretly show off your Lunight pride!
次は、こちら！もっと一緒にぬいぐるみキーホルダー♡ 2024年の誕生日記念グッズで登場したぬいぐるみキーホルダーの第2弾なのだ！今回のグッズたちと合わせて、大人カッコいい衣装に身を包んでいるルーたんと言えばスタジャンを気長にお揃いにするのだ！
Next, this! 'More Together' Plushie Keychain♡ This is the 2nd installment of the plushie keychains from the 2024 birthday commemoration! Pair it with these new goods, as Lutan dressed in a mature, cool outfit matches the stadium jacket!
では、最後に改めてフルセットを見てみましょう！
Now, let's take another look at the full set!
今回はカッコ可愛いがテーマだからグッズもカッコよくて使いやすいものが多いのなら！フルセットを購入すると、かんざきパパが描いてくれたイラストを...
Since the theme this time is 'cool and cute,' many of the goods are cool and easy to use! If you purchase the full set, you'll get the illustration drawn by Kanzaki-papa...
かった！
Got it!
チケット風カードが特典でついてくるのな！
A ticket-style card comes as a bonus, nano!
数量限定のフルセット特典はジギッツサイン入りチケット風カード！
Quantity-limited full set bonus: a ticket-style card with a digital signature!
通常盤は箔押し複製サイン入りのチケット風カードなのな！
The regular edition is a ticket-style card with foil-stamped duplicate signature, nano!
みんなぜひゲットしてねー！
Everyone, please be sure to get it!
グッズはこの後販売開始なのなー！
The goods will go on sale right after this!
そして大切なお知らせ2つ目！
And the second important announcement!
この後はなたんの新曲第6弾を歌うのなー！
After this, I'll be singing Natan's 6th new song, nano!
タイトルはプリプリプリンセス！
The title is Puripuri Princess!
作詞作曲はナユタン星人さん、なたんの可愛いおねだりソングなのなね！
Lyrics and music by Nayutalien-san, it's Natan's cute pleading song, nano!
この後24時にリリース！その後MVもね、公開されるのでそちらもお楽しみにー！
Releasing at midnight tonight! The MV will also be released after that, so please look forward to it!
ということで、この後新曲を歌っちゃうのな！聞いてください、プリプリプリンセス！
With that said, I'll be singing my new song right now! Please listen to it: Puripuri Princess!
プリプリプリンセス(なのら！)
Puripuri Princess, nano!
むかしむかしあるところに ちゅか現在進行形！いまここに！
Once upon a time, right now in progress, right here!
プリンセスがおりました
A princess appeared.
ちゅか目の前に！わかってんの！？
Right before your eyes! Do you even get it!?
ある日 姫は言いました 「甘いモノを所望する！」
One day, the princess said, "I demand sweets!"
でも本音はいつも違うので キミは言います
But her true feelings are always different, so you say,
「わちゅわなどー！」困らせたいんじゃないのにないのかまってほしいだけ
"What-what is this?!" Not that I want to trouble you, I just want your attention!
キミの国のイチバンは 鏡よ鏡よ使うこともなくわたしがいいの！
Number one in your kingdom, without even needing a magic mirror, it has to be me!
だからっ♪ お姫さまにさせてねマイダーリン
So... let me be your princess, my darling!
比較的ムリめなおねだり 言わせてね ちょびっとでもいいから
Even if it's a bit of an unreasonable request, let me say it, even just a little bit,
スキの魔法で背伸びしたい(プリンセス！)
I want to reach higher with the magic of love (Princess!)
キミをときめかせると誓いますか(はい！) よそ見なんてしないと誓いますか(はい！)
Do you promise to make your heart flutter? (Yes!) Do you promise never to look away? (Yes!)
ワガママでアママなプリンセスを キミだけにしたいの！(プリプリ！プリンセス！)
I want this selfish, sweet princess to be only for you! (Puripuri! Princess!)
甘いモノっちゅーかキミといたいだけ (プリプリ！プリンセス！)
More than sweets, I just want to be with you! (Puripuri! Princess!)
まるっと喜怒哀楽ごと愛してねっ！
Love all my ups and downs completely!
12時の鐘が鳴ったって 覚めない夢をみていたって
Even if the 12 o'clock bell rings, even if I'm dreaming an unawakening dream,
それもキミに出会うための ずっと続いてる物語
Even that is a continuing story in order to meet you.
つないだ手と手離れない様 ぎゅっと握ってくれないと 恐ろしい魔女に食べられちゃう！
If you don't hold my connected hands tightly so they won't part, I'll be eaten by a scary witch!
ってまた変なふうに伝えちゃう――
Or rather, I end up saying it in a weird way again—
そうやってずっとキミのこと 考えてしまうのに キミの国はどうなってる！？
Even though I always think about you like that, how is your kingdom doing!?
国名も国服もスタチューも法律も わたしじゃないの！？ないの！？
Even the country name, national costume, statue, and laws... aren't they me?! Aren't they?!
お姫さまにさせてねマイダーリン 比較的ムリめなおねだり
Let me be your princess, my darling, a somewhat impossible request,
言わせてね 叶えなくてもいい ほんとはもう叶ってる――
Let me say it, even if it doesn't come true, it actually already came true—
お姫さまにさせてねマイダーリン 圧倒的ラヴな本音も
Let me be your princess, my darling, even my overwhelmingly loving true feelings,
包ませて清楚さそなヴェールで キミだけにみつけて欲しい！(プリンセス！)
Wrapped in a pure veil, I want only you to find me! (Princess!)
もっとアイをくれると誓いますか(はい！) ちゃかそなのキホン違いますか(はい！)
Do you promise to give me more love? (Yes!) Isn't that the basics of the basics? (Yes!)
ワガママでアママなプリンセスは キミだけにしたいから
Because I want this selfish, sweet princess to be only for you,
練習中な特注なプリンセスを もっとキミとさせてねっ！
Let me play princess, custom-made and in training, even more with you!
(プリプリ！プリンセス！) 甘いモノっちゅーかキミといたいだけ
(Puripuri! Princess!) More than sweets, I just want to be with you
(プリプリ！プリンセス！) まるっと喜怒哀楽ごと愛してねっ！
(Puripuri! Princess!) Love all my ups and downs completely!
もっともっと楽しめよ乙女
More and more, enjoy yourselves, maidens!
みんなに気づかれないように
So that nobody notices,
見えない壁も乗り越えて
climbing over unseen walls.
お気に入りの服かぶり
Wearing my favorite clothes,
今日も今日とてゴロゴロして
I'm lazing around again today.
大丈夫なの？ポテチ片手に
Is this okay? With chips in one hand,
パソコンとにらめっこしよう
let's stare down the computer.
だってましゅまろ菓子をかじれば
Because if I bite into marshmallow sweets,
歩く姿はユリの花
my walking figure is like a lily flower.
誰もがうらやむ完璧ジェンヌ
The perfect star everyone envies—
ほら限界を叩き壊した
look, I've smashed through my limits!
さあ、もっと鳴らそうよ
Come on, let's make it ring out more!
いつでも胸は騒ぐものさ ねえコンボ
My heart always races, hey, combo!
ずっと ずっと ゲームはおともだち
Always, always, games are my friends.
お兄ちゃんは厳しいけど
Big bro is strict, though,
ずっと ずっと 許してくれるの
he always, always forgives me.
わがままお嬢様は
This selfish princess
大好きの裏返し
is just showing her love in reverse!
外では猫かぶり
Putting on a good face outside,
今日も明日も演じるので
I play the part today and tomorrow.
そこで今日の笑顔武器に
Using today's smile as my weapon,
友達にバレないように
so my friends won't find out!
だって二刀流座れば満杯
Because sitting with dual styles fills the room,
歩く姿はちんちくりん
and my walking figure is pint-sized.
誰でも癒やせる愛嬌マスコット
A lovable mascot that heals anyone—
高い壁を越えるまでパーティーナイト
party night until we cross high walls!
舞台の始まりだ
The stage begins now!
室内で優雅な女の子演じてみても
Even if I try acting like an elegant girl indoors,
お兄ちゃんだけはだませないけど
I can't fool big bro, though.
怒られたくないも素直になれない
I don't want to get scolded, yet I can't be honest.
嫌われたくないも素直にいえない
I don't want to be disliked, yet I can't say it straight.
ありがとうと何度も示そう
Let's show our thanks over and over.
だって世界甘えいんじゃ
Because the world is all about being spoiled!
お兄ちゃんなんて知らない
Big bro, I don't even know you!
なんて二人で一つだって、だって！
As if we're two in one—really!
それが兄弟でしょ、一蓮托生
That's what siblings are, sharing the same fate.
二人きりの運命共同体
A destiny-bound duo, just the two of us!
今日だって重圧を笑い飛ばして
Laughing off the pressure again today,
もっともっと楽しんだもの勝ちでしょ
whoever enjoys it more wins, right?
天真爛漫スマイルでゆっとゆっと
With an innocent smile, ever so gently,
心掴んじゃうのやりたい放題は
capturing hearts while doing whatever we want—
世話しないの裏返し
that's just the flip side of being restless!
このあとはMV公開!
[MV premiere coming up next!]